The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Break !
To win this battle,
you must do 3 things.
The first is
to break the demonic formation
to force him to appear.
The formation is destroyed.
Soldiers, hear my orders !
Assist the Sky Demon Envoy
in breaching the city !
Kill !
Full army
relocation !
You all...
are courting death !
The power of the Fire Demon !
Our countries have fought for countless years
but this is the first time the Fire Demon acted.
Why today ?
We Ancient Demon Spirits guard the 9 countries.
We shouldn't interfere in wars.
But if the Fire Demon senses my aura on you...
I'm sure he'll come out enraged !
He isn't weaker than me.
This means...
it will be a true life or death trial for you.
Fire Demon
Bei Luo's stench...
How dare you lay a finger on my territory !
Well...
Very well !
Since you broke the rules first,
I will let you know
the meaning of...
an Ancient Demon's wrath !
Order the army
to retreat.
Entire army, retreat !
You mere ants
shall be incinerated
never to be reborn !
The Fire Demon is too strong for us.
Brother Wang,
withdraw !
Do you still think
you can contend with me all alone ?
Devil Energy ?
Interesting...
Demonic Finger !
The power of this finger
is far above your cultivation level.
However...
you're still an ant trying to shake a tree.
You attack so aggressively...
What does Bei Luo expect to do
by sending you here ?
Is he naive enough
to think that you could beat me
with your mere strength ?
Dao of the Underworld...
Underworld River !
1 000 000 strands of slaughter energy,
fuse into one !
With your strength alone,
it will be impossible to defeat him.
So the second thing...
is to find a way to get within 100 zhang of him
Note: 1 zhang = 3m
and use this spell
condense a body for me
and allow me to fight the Fire Demon.
This boy is just an Ascendant.
The Sky Demon must have a plan if he sent him.
Little ant,
this game
has come to an end !
Demonic Spell...
Demon Slaughter !
The Fire Demon's Life Artifact !
Die !
Stop !
Given the gap in cultivation,
the Stop Spell will last for less than a breath.
But it should be enough !
Useless tricks !
I'm within 100 zhang,
Bei Luo !
Impossible !
How did you break the restriction to leave the city ?
We pay respects to the Ancestor !
This is...
the aura of an Ancient God !
By using his blood
to condense a body
and by linking our Divine Senses,
I was able to bypass the restriction
to walk out of the Sky Demon Country.
Despicable !
The Ancient Demon Spirit fragments have been separated for too long.
If we don't fuse soon,
we will completely dissipate to return to the heavens and the earth.
Our fusion will begin the process of rebirth !
As for the others...
I will also devour them one by one.
You wish !
The third thing you need to do
Fire Demon Tower
Fire Demon City
is also the most important.
Enter the Fire Demon Tower
and destroy the Fire Demon statue.
Statues are the source of our power.
If it's destroyed,
we will win this battle.
Once I devour the Fire Demon,
I will tell you where your friend is.
Fire Demon avatar
Peak Late stage Ascendant
The power of the Fire Demon and his avatar both come from the statue.
If it's destroyed, they both die.
I will do my best to hold back his original body
and help you kill the avatar
to destroy the statue as soon as possible.
God Slaying Chariot !
You condensed a body with his blood
but it's only a temporary measure.
Within my Fire Demon Country,
you can't defeat me !
Wait until I devour that brat with the Ancient God aura.
One day, the one who unites the 9 demons
will be me !
Treacherous brat !
I am
your opponent !
Get away from me !
Wang Lin,
now !
Ling Tianhou's sword energy !
Stop !
No !!!
We've been apart for too long.
It's time to end this !
This is...
7-colored Space
Wang Lin's Sea of Consciousness
Senior Situ,
I've mastered the Attraction technique !
These are...
all the spells I learned.
After you destroy the statue,
I will help you
to obtain the Ancient Demon inheritance.
You may choose one spell to cultivate to completion.
Apart from you,
I've only given this inheritance
to two other cultivators.
The second one
was one of the most talented
I have ever met.
Who was it ?
Sun Yun.
That day, I saw a similar scene
within the All-Seer's Sea of Consciousness...
This 7-colored space is a spell that should only be unlocked
after Illusory Yin and Corporeal Yang.
But now, with the Ancient Demon inheritance,
I am experiencing it ahead of time.
I can choose one spell to cultivate to completion...
This is...
a strand of slaughter energy ?
How can this be ?
If this is true,
when I cultivate the Celestial Slaughter Art to completion,
I will die on the spot
and become one of the All-Seer's Life Seals...
The Celestial Slaughter Art
is far too vicious.
Fortunately, I haven't fully cultivated it.
Otherwise, I'm afraid I would have fallen for it.
I wonder if Sun Yun's disappearance
was also related to this...
Purple Cloud Pavilion
All-Seer...
I told you that
if you don't betray me,
I would never betray you in my life.
But if you betray me...
How was your comprehension ?
Bei Luo
Ancient Demon
Senior Bei Luo.
I successfully devoured the Fire Demon fragment.
I don't need to use your blood anymore
to step out of the Sky Demon Country.
Within 100 years,
I will fuse with the remaining 7 fragments.
At that time...
I, Ancient Demon Bei Luo,
will be reborn.
In this battle,
your contribution was indispensable.
While you were meditating during the past few months,
I found the location of your friend's Divine Sense.
That place collapses
once every 500 years.
When it collapses,
it will suck numerous artifacts and Spirit Beasts from outside.
It's the root of the tide in the outside world.
However, this place...
has become a bottomless abyss
after the countless tides.
Tide Abyss
Water Demon Country
People also call it...
the Tide Abyss.
Your friend is in there.
That place is unfathomably deep,
are you certain you want to go ?
I need to repay my friend's kindness.
I must go.
So be it.
There are 6 entrances to the Tide Abyss
but only a single exit
located in Fire Demon Country.
I can only sense that your friend is closest to the Water Demon Country's entrance.
But I can't find
his exact location.
Take this.
Just merge your Divine Sense into it,
and you'll be able to see everything inside the Tide Abyss.
Thank you, Senior Ancient Demon.
I shall take my leave.
This boy has the aura of the royal Ancient God bloodline...
If I could devour him,
it would be a great tonic.
But if my Ancient Demon Clan survived until now,
the Ancient Gods might still be alive.
Devouring this boy
isn't worth the trouble.
However...
while I, Bei Luo, can resist this temptation,
I wonder if Ancient Devil Ta Jia
will be able to do the same.
If my guess is correct,
they should also be within the Tide Abyss.
I must find Senior Zhou Yi as soon as possible !
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.